[♪ pop music playing]
PERFECT CROWN
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
WERE FILMED SAFELY
[♪ tender music plays]
[I-AN] You said you'd let me fly.
Why are you the one flying?
Let's switch. I can hold you.
-Forget it.
-Why not? Come on…
[yelps]
-[grunts]
-[Huiju yelps]
[Huiju pants]
[distorted breath]
[distorted exhale]
[Huiju grunts]
[gasps]
[♪ gentle pop music plays]
Your Royal Highness.
Are you hurt anywhere?
You said I can do whatever I want.
PERFECT CROWN
EPISODE 7
[I-AN clears throat]
-[Youngseon] Your Ladyship!
-[Yeongmun] Your Royal Highness.
Why were you out so late
without the Royal Guard?
Well, we were… You know…
They must have wanted some alone time.
STYLE
::cue()
[Youngseon chuckles]
Did you go somewhere nice?
-No!
[sighs]
He wanted some fresh air,
so we went for a drive. Beep-beep.
Then you should've let us know!
Aide Choi is a complete mess
because you two weren't reachable.
[clears throat]
Listen.
-You should…
-Pardon?
-What? Huh?
-Yes?
You should get some rest.
[♪ playful music playing]
Aren't you tired?
I am.
Gosh, I'm so tired.
[♪ gentle music plays]
[exclaims quietly]
[sighs]
[muffled exclaiming]
[pants]
I mean, it's no big deal.
We were just caught up in the moment.
I mean, it's not like
I threw myself at him.
Hmm.
[sighs]
[whimpers]
[squeakily] Why did I do that?
[gasps]
[chuckles softly]
It's fine.
You're a grown,
functioning member of society.
[chuckles]
It's not fine at all!
I'm so screwed. What am I going to do now?
[footsteps outside]
[I-AN clears throat]
Seong Huiju.
[whispers] What now?
[chuckles softly]
[sighs]
[heartbeat thumping]
Are you nuts? Why are you racing?
[clicks tongue]
[sighs]
STYLE
::cue()
What are you doing?
[yelps]
[♪ dreamy music playing]
Off to work already?
Oh!
[chuckling] Yes, that's right.
I need to get to work.
I need to work. I'm the CEO.
Need to figure out my successor and all.
This and that.
What a lovely day it is today.
See you.
[chuckles]
[church bell tolls]
[♪ organ music plays]
In the name of the Father,
the Son, and the Holy Spirit,
Amen.
[chuckles]
You see,
I'm actually not Catholic. Is that okay?
Well, the man upstairs is a forgiving one.
Please go ahead.
[sighs]
Then, by chance,
do you think I could get an exorcism?
Pardon me?
It's just that…
I feel like I'm possessed right now.
[whimpering]
Oh no!
Could we maybe work something out?
I can make a very generous donation
to the church.
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[Huiju] Seriously?
"Not one to begrudge"?
Yet he just did that.
I even wore white for this.
Seong Huiju?
Oh.
Jeongwoo.
[chuckles softly]
What brings you here?
Oh, a cab.
[chuckles]
That's not what I'm asking.
Why are you here?
I thought you weren't religious.
I know, right?
Wait here. I'll be right out.
No, I can just go
by myself…
[sighs]
[phone buzzing]
PRINCE
[clears throat]
[vocalizes]
Yes, Your Royal Highness.
Are you free?
Right now?
We have something on the calendar
for wedding planning,
but you said you were busy.
I see.
Shall I reschedule it?
No, I have time.
Let's go, Huiju.
That was quick.
STYLE
::cue()
Your Royal Highness, I'll call you later.
See you later.
JUNIOR ALUM
[sighs]
Shall we?
I'm coming.
[Huiju] I told you,
I could've taken a cab.
It's fine. It's on the way anyway.
[chuckles]
Do you like driving too?
-That's random.
-The Grand Prince
smiles when he drives too.
He says it feels like he's flying.
[chuckles]
He can be so childlike sometimes.
[♪ gentle piano plays]
[sighs]
CASTLE BEAUTY
Bye. Thanks for the ride.
-Huiju.
-Yes?
Don't get too attached.
What?
It'll drive up the divorce settlement.
Be it in money, reputation…
or your heart.
[scoffs]
Do you think I'm an idiot?
-[chuckles softly]
-[scoffs]
Bye.
[sighs]
[scoffs]
Who does he take me for?
Someone who can't distinguish
between business and pleasure?
Seriously?
[scoffs]
[Hyejeong] Ms. Seong.
Pull the affiliate numbers
and line them up by revenue.
Throw this out for me.
[door opens]
[Hyejeong] Why, all of a sudden?
They must all be thrilled
that I'm stepping down.
Planning to slack off
without the revenue-obsessed boss
breathing down their necks.
So you want to whip them into shape?
Yes.
[♪ dramatic music plays]
I'll remind them they'll be
royally screwed if revenue drops.
Okay, I'll get to it now.
Have Seong Taeju meet me there.
The Senior Managing Director?
AUSPICIOUS DATES
FOR GRAND PRINCE I-AN'S WEDDING
These are the dates
the Royal Secretariat and the Cabinet
have proposed
for the Grand Prince's nuptials.
All are auspicious days,
so Your Majesty may select
whichever you see fit.
[announcer] Your Majesty,
Grand Prince I-AN has arrived.
Show him in.
STYLE
::cue()
Your Majesty.
I heard you were selecting
the day for my nuptials.
I am considering choosing this date.
Is there a particular reason?
Is it not the earliest day?
[chuckles softly]
May I take a look?
[♪ pensive music plays]
I would prefer this day.
For any particular reason?
We will need…
some time.
I shall choose this date then.
JULY 3RD, LUNAR JUNE 9TH
[Huiju] I'm just here to support the team.
No need to be nervous.
You are our top-performing affiliate
in terms of sales.
The new collection that just launched
is performing well
with the 25-35 demographic.
This necklace is part of
the same set as your earrings today.
Would you like to try it on?
-Sure.
-All right.
Hmm…
[chuckles]
And it'll stay that way, right?
Pardon?
I don't think I'll ever stop
being curious about numbers.
I might be getting married,
but I'll still be keeping an eye
and ear on things.
Of course, ma'am.
We'll continue doing our best.
[chuckles]
Huiju.
Did I ask you to invite that gremlin too?
It wasn't me.
[Dayeong giggles]
I insisted on coming along.
I missed you, you know.
You could've just called
if you had something to say.
Making me come all this way…
[clicks tongue]
Babe, check this out.
This would look perfect on you.
Come on. This new collection is nice.
Try this on.
It's… Whoa, amazing.
This will be the first handover.
What?
My shares.
Right, your shares…
What?
Wait.
[♪ jazz music plays]
You mean it?
You're really going to hand it over
to me? All of Castle Beauty?
-Should I not?
-You should.
Come on. Why would you say such a thing?
-I will kill you if you fail.
-What?
[scoffs]
You heard me.
[mouthing] I will kill you.
Is that brat setting a trap to murder me?
No.
No?
Yeah, definitely not.
STYLE
::cue()
Did you really mean that?
What?
You have other options,
like hiring a non-owner executive.
There's also Director Choi.
It sounds like
you never want me to come back.
-What?
-Father and everyone will finally get it
once Seong Taeju takes over.
"Oh, right.
Seong Huiju is leagues above Seong Taeju.
Thus, the Castle Group successor must be
Seong Huiju and no one else."
I see.
Which affiliate is next?
Since when were they an affiliate?
I was told you confirmed it.
Were they wrong?
When?
-This morning.
-When did I…
-Are you free?
-I have time.
I did that.
I most certainly did.
Seriously?
Let's go.
[sighs]
[whimpers softly]
What the…
You're unbelievable.
How pretty.
This will be your wedding robe,
so please let us know right away
if you feel any discomfort.
-Sure.
-Please take your place.
Ms. Do.
-Can you turn to the right?
-Sure.
[Huiju] Hmm?
Oh!
What's wrong?
Stay still.
[clears throat]
-[Lady Choi] Are you feeling unwell?
-What?
-[Hyejeong] Are you sick?
-Royal Physician!
-What's wrong?
-No, I'm fine.
-Oh!
-What is it?
STYLE
::cue()
No, I'm just feeling
a little hot. That's all.
No, I think you have a fever.
I'm just a little hot. Too many layers.
Her Ladyship is overheated.
Lower the room temperature.
Yes, ma'am.
-Please hurry.
-No, I…
It will be cooler in no time.
Isn't it time for our next appointment?
[Hyeon] Your next appointment?
After this, a royal physician
will come by for a health assessment.
Tomorrow, we have dinner
at Ms. Seong's family home.
What? "Family home"?
As in my family? Why?
It's customary for a future son-in-law
to offer his greetings to his in-laws.
Mmm.
Ah. The chairman's office was notified.
They already confirmed it.
[Hyeon] Thank you.
I'm off to handle the Marriage Proposal
and Wedding Gift Delivery ceremonies.
Marriage Proposal ceremony?
Marriage Proposal
and Wedding Gift Delivery ceremonies?
[♪ ethereal music plays]
"This is a royal edict
for Hyeonguk of the Seong Family.
The King proclaimed…"
"When Heaven and Earth first parted,
human order came into being.
Through the union of husband and wife,
the ancestors and royal line are upheld."
Hand me another piece of paper.
Yes, Your Majesty.
In accordance with tradition,
Chief Attendant Min Jeongwoo
and Deputy Attendant Choi Hyeon
shall observe proper decorum
and carry out the Marriage Proposal.
[Hyeon] "Thus is the royal edict.
Let all be duly informed."
I will now outline the proceedings.
Traditionally, the wedding rites
begin at the bride's home.
However, given the security risks
and His Royal Highness's regency,
they will instead be held
at his private residence.
Then we'll be
at his private residence as well?
Yes, that's right. [chuckles]
And I also have this for you…
Just a moment.
I put together an outline
of the wedding rites, just in case.
[Hyeonguk] Can you
speak a bit faster?
-Pardon?
-I had to postpone two meetings for this.
Yes, sir. Here you go.
FATHER
Ms. Seong.
Hey.
They're all waiting for you.
[Lady Choi] Why have you stepped outside?
Are you still overheated?
No, it's not that.
Then you must return
for your health assessment.
STYLE
::cue()
Okay.
You will have
a more thorough exam
at Royal Seoul Hospital.
Today's examination will assess
constitution and fertility.
Pardon?
Yes?
Mmm… No, it's nothing. Please continue.
[Lady Choi chuckles]
Heirs are precious within the palace.
Once your health is duly confirmed,
arrangements for your union shall--
"Arrangements"?
What sort of arrangements?
The conjugal union symbolizes
the harmony of yin and yang.
Yin must flow to yang,
and yang must incline toward yin.
Once proper comportment facilitates that,
an auspicious day and hour shall be set…
-[physician] Hold on.
-What is it?
Her pulse is elevated.
Uh…
-Are you feeling unwell?
-[chuckles]
Wait, hold on.
Could this be
a post-accident complication?
[chuckling]
No, it's nothing like that. Be quiet.
[Lady Choi]
Then do you have a preexisting condition?
No, not at all.
No preexisting condition. [chuckles]
[I-AN] That is enough.
I wish to speak with her in private.
Give us the room.
[Lady Choi] Yes, Your Royal Highness.
[Huiju clears throat]
[hums]
Something bothering you?
What?
You've been acting strangely.
What do you mean?
You're the one
who's been acting strangely.
-Me?
-You're being unnecessarily sweet to me.
While everyone was watching,
you, like, brushed
the hair out of my face.
And your eyes…
You keep looking at me
with those doe eyes.
My eyes have never changed.
That's not true.
Is this about yesterday?
[shrill grunt]
I'm fine.
About what?
About last night.
[chuckles]
I'm fine with it.
It's not like we're kids or anything.
I mean, if the vibe is right…
Why not?
And with the vibe we had going yesterday,
even if it had been a complete stranger,
anyone would've done the same. Yeah…
A complete stranger…
Pardon?
Not for me.
[♪ gentle music plays]
What?
What does that mean?
I didn't do it just because
I was caught up in the moment.
I did it…
because it's you.
STYLE
::cue()
The Grand Prince is perturbed?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Ms. Seong was by earlier in the day.
He has been a bit agitated ever since.
The date has been set,
yet he remains agitated…
I shall go for a walk with him.
Did something happen to upset you?
You appear troubled.
Could you be upset
about what happened yesterday evening?
Of course not.
Then,
did you have an argument with Ms. Seong?
It seems you wish that to be so.
I am merely worried.
You two come from different worlds.
Perfect accord cannot be easily attained.
And you?
Did you attain accord?
[chuckles]
You and my brother
grew up in the same world.
Did you two…
arrive at happiness?
How can I go by myself?
They are expecting both of us.
What would you have me do?
Your Majesty.
[sighs]
Has my brother run off again?
[clicks tongue]
I shall accompany you.
If we say that the Crown Prince is unwell,
they would scarcely consider it
improper that I, the Grand Prince,
accompany you in his stead.
That would only prompt Father
to reprimand you.
[chuckles]
I'm reprimanded every day anyway.
Is there any place
for happiness in a royal union?
[I-AN] I did it
because it's you.
[sighs]
PRINCE
No.
So what?
Should we just date a little
since we're going to divorce anyway?
[in English] Nope.
STYLE
::cue()
[sighs]
MARRIAGE CONTRACT
4. DIVORCE WITHIN THREE YEARS
AT THE LATEST
[♪ dramatic music plays]
[screaming, clamoring]
[Im] You must hurry.
[Yun breathing shakily]
[in Korean] Why are you in such a state?
Please get up, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty?
The press
will soon spread the news
of His Majesty's tragedy.
You must secure
the Crown Prince's accession.
His Majesty had abandoned
the Crown Prince.
He wished to depose the Crown Prince…
and abdicate
in favor of Grand Prince I-AN.
What do you mean?
He even drew up a royal edict!
[breathing shakily]
I am certain…
His Majesty will understand me.
This was all for the Crown Prince's sake.
What in the world
have you done?
I…
I burned it all to the ground.
[sighs]
[safe beeps]
[♪ dramatic music plays]
STYLE
::cue()
AS SUCH, I INTEND TO ABDICATE
AND BE SUCCEEDED
BY GRAND PRINCE I-AN
[♪ epic music playing]
"I am most pleased to see you again,
Your Royal Highness." And then…
"It is my great honor."
-Damn it…
-Babe.
Did you not dry your hair?
I tried doing it like His Royal Highness.
Do you not like it?
Why would you copy his style?
Too many feelers? I just thought…
You're so much more handsome than him!
-Really?
-Who does Taeju belong to?
To Dayeong. Ah…
-Stop it. Come on.
-Why isn't Father coming down?
[clears throat, inhales sharply]
But what if Father
does a repeat of yesterday?
He wouldn't.
Father? Father!
I can hear you perfectly fine.
[clears throat]
Father. [chuckles]
You should lighten up a little.
We should be celebrating today.
-[in English] Smile.
-[in Korean] That's right.
You can hate your own kid,
but you shouldn't hate your son-in-law.
Especially, when he's Grand Prince I-AN.
Just look at me.
After falling for Dayeong,
I bow down to her father like it's my job.
Do you see how Grand Prince I-AN
is wasting no time?
He must be beyond smitten
with her too. I swear--
That's enough of that nonsense.
[huffs]
[Hyeon] If I could just have
your attention for a moment.
Once we arrive, there might be a bit
of a crowd waiting to see you two.
Please remember to smile
when you step out.
Ms. Seong, you can just follow
the Grand Prince's lead and wave.
And the Royal Guard?
We should be fine.
We dispatched double the normal amount.
-What about…
Do we have an end time?
There's no rush.
You should just enjoy your meal,
but at the minimum,
we're thinking four hours…
Four hours?
[Hyeon] Well, you see,
if you leave too early,
it may be seen as discourteous.
If too late, the other members
of the royal family will grow jealous.
[chuckles] I'd appreciate it if you
kept these things in mind.
Please forgive the delayed greetings.
Father.
[clears throat] Well,
we are very honored to host you,
Your Royal Highness.
My dear younger sister is not perforated.
I mean, not perfect.
We hope she does not prove an impediment.
-And…
-[clears throat]
I, Hyeonguk of the Seong Family,
offer you my greetings,
Your Royal Highness.
This is my son.
I'm the Senior Managing Director
of Castle Group
and his soon-to-be successor…
Yes, right.
I remember, Brother.
[chuckles] Yes, I see.
Uh… [chuckles]
"Brother"? Insane.
You mean, "Your Royal Highness."
[chuckles] Yes, right. He already… Yeah.
[both chuckle]
[sighs]
STYLE
::cue()
I mean, I know it's just an…
just an act and all,
but they're so stiff
around each other, aren't they?
I'm so scared they're going to get caught.
I hear you.
I heard it was super awkward
during the health assessment yesterday.
I mean, can you imagine
how tense she must've been?
To make her heart pound like that?
But…
-Don't you think it's excessive?
-My thoughts exactly.
-Maybe they're falling for each other.
-What?
I mean, they actually look like
they just started dating.
Just started dating…
Oh?
[phone chimes]
[gasps] I need to go.
I'll come with you.
No, you should finish all this first.
I'm off.
Okay. See you later.
[sighs]
[♪ romantic music plays]
[Taeju] Yes, thanks.
[clears throat] Thank you.
I'm actually the CEO
of Castle Hotel as well.
I had some of our chefs come by
to cook this. How is it?
You're not the CEO yet.
That handover hasn't happened yet.
Must you bring that up now?
[stammers] It's almost done.
It's all very good, Brother.
Oh… [chuckles]
Is it?
I'm so glad.
[inhales sharply]
Can I ask when you two started dating?
-Pardon?
-Well, you see,
she used to have terrible taste in men.
What do they call it?
You know, the ones you carry around.
Who cares about that now?
Oh, right. Trophy boys.
She used to be really into trophy boys.
They were always so skinny.
But somehow, she landed
a really solid husband.
-[smacks table]
-Seong…
Dear brother.
Relax. It's a compliment.
Just look at Our Royal Highness.
He's so tall. Almost as tall
as the doorframe. And his shoulders…
Yeah, they're almost
as broad as this table.
-That's a real man for you…
-[chuckles]
He's just trying to say
that you make a really nice couple.
Yeah, that's right.
-Stop drinking.
-Okay.
-Yeah, a nice couple. Mmm…
-[sighs]
[Hyeonguk] Please…
cherish her.
She spent her whole life
thinking highly of herself,
so I had hoped
she'd end up with someone
a bit beneath her.
I cannot help but be concerned
about her marrying into the royal family.
I will do my best to make sure
you have nothing to worry--
If that was all it took,
I would not worry.
[♪ tense music plays]
That place is known
for its troubles and tragedies, is it not?
[chuckles]
That doesn't
quite hold up, does it?
Who are you trying to kid?
Am I wrong? [sighs]
Where was that ever-worried father
when I got into that car accident?
It just doesn't add up, does it?
As you can see, she is still a child.
-She has her shortcomings--
-[smacks table]
That's enough small talk, isn't it?
Don't you have a wedding gift for us?
I mean, when Taeju got married,
you gave Dayeong's family
company shares and even a building.
All on a silver platter.
STYLE
::cue()
[coughs]
Your one and only daughter
is getting married.
Surely, you must have something.
How about
a generous donation to the crown?
[Taeju] Hey.
You're making
His Royal Highness uncomfortable.
[sighs]
You can finish this meal without me.
I thought I could practice restraint…
[sucks teeth, inhales sharply]
…but it's just too hard.
-[sighs]
-[Taeju] Hmm…
Let me check on her.
[sighs]
Seong Huiju.
[Huiju breathing slowly, deeply]
Just let me be for a second.
I'll come back down
once my anger subsides a bit.
[I-AN grunts, sighs]
What?
Are you having second thoughts?
Because my family is such a hot mess?
You must have a bad memory.
If you remembered
what Queen Mother said to me,
there's no way you'd say that.
That's true.
Doesn't it seem like your father likes me?
-You believed that?
-Should I not?
That doting, concerned father bit
is all an act.
The result of him running
the numbers and sizing up
what he could gain by using you.
Who cares?
As long as I'm genuine.
[♪ tender song playing]
I have a great deal that you do not,
and if you ask for it,
I fully intend to provide it.
By chance,
do you have feelings for me?
-All of a sudden?
-Then was I
your first… or something?
What?
I mean… [sucks teeth]
It's true. I can be quite a femme fatale.
But still,
your eyes are sparkling a little too much.
[scoffs]
[laughs]
I do like you.
STYLE
::cue()
And it's my first time.
Restraint always followed desire.
But it's not easy this time.
What? Having second thoughts?
Worried I won't divorce you?
You won't?
Don't worry.
I don't want to keep you bound to me.
You should just accept it all.
Whether it be money, honor,
or my heart…
[♪ song continuing]
I've always had more money than you.
Always?
Always have.
-"Always have"?
-Always will.
[chuckles]
[♪ song continuing]
[phone buzzing]
JEONGWOO
What? Pick it up.
Hey, Jeongwoo.
Yeah, it's over. We're heading back
to the private residence.
Yeah, he's right next to me.
Sure. Hold on.
[Jeongwoo] Your Royal Highness,
did it go well?
Yeah.
My father-in-law loves me.
Really? [chuckles]
I guess you didn't fight
with your father today.
Do you think I just go around
starting fights everywhere?
[Jeongwoo chuckles]
And Taeju? Did he behave?
He was whatever.
I still can't tell if handing over
the reins to him was a good idea.
Yeah. [chuckles]
I know, right?
What about you? Are you done with work?
I'll see you on our wedding day.
I'm sad about leaving too.
[car door opens]
[car door shuts]
[chuckles]
STYLE
::cue()
How did it go?
Did the chairman like him?
-Of course, he did. How could he not?
-Earlier, His Royal Highness was like,
"I'm sad about leaving too."
-He said that before he left.
-[giggling]
Was His Royal Highness nervous?
Did he do well?
Have you been waiting for me
to ask about that?
-Yes.
-They couldn't even eat.
They were all so nervous.
-Still?
-Yes.
[sighs, scoffs]
I know it's late,
but should we grab a bite?
-Yes.
-Yes please!
What about that new place?
You said that place was delicious.
-Where is this place?
-Yeah, we should go there.
[server] Enjoy.
Thank you. All right, then.
Eat up now.
It'll all be
my treat tonight.
-Thank you.
-Thank you so much.
[exclaims]
Mmm!
-It's so good.
-[chuckles]
Your Ladyship, you should have some too.
Poor thing.
You must've been too nervous to eat.
You must be a ball of nerves
with the wedding approaching.
Come on, a lot of people go on diets
before their wedding.
As if.
She's already light as a feather.
Why would she go on a diet?
[groans] I'm taking
a night off from that diet.
-Eat up.
-Excellent.
Mmm…
Mmm!
We've been meaning to throw you
a little bridal shower.
Maybe we can pick up a cake later?
[Yeongmun] Her Ladyship must be tired.
Just eat up.
Areum, why aren't you eating?
I thought you liked this place.
Ah… I'm just taking my time.
You should eat up too.
-Hmm…
-Here, eat this.
It's good.
[♪ dramatic music plays]
This is the Treasury's revised proposal.
Please take a look.
[phone rings]
[assistant] Sir,
His Royal Highness is here for you.
He is?
It's not on your schedule.
You busy?
Can I get you anything?
I like Seong Huiju.
I thought you should know.
[scoffs]
And does my knowing that
change anything?
It'll make sure
you mind your conduct.
[chuckles]
Does Huiju know too?
STYLE
::cue()
I'm talking about myself right now.
Not her.
Don't make…
things difficult for Huiju.
What?
That's not
what she wants from you.
Where's Seong Huiju?
Ah… She went into a board meeting
two hours ago.
She should be done by now.
She's probably in transit now.
She said she was visiting an affiliate
right after the meeting.
-[sighs] She'll have no time to eat.
-Exactly.
Her shares and duties must be transferred
before the wedding.
She has so much on her plate.
Meaning poor Ms. Do
must also be suffering…
Thanks for your hard work.
DON'T FORGET TO EAT…
[chuckles]
She's everywhere.
-Why are they taking that down?
-Pardon?
Oh, that? It needs to be taken down now.
Her Royal Highness cannot engage
in personal promotion.
[sighs]
[I-AN] Don't forget to eat
just because you're busy.
Why'd you pull that ad already?
Make money while you still can.
-[Hyejeong] Ms. Seong.
-What?
-Continue.
-Yes, ma'am.
Next, we are developing plans
for local marketing campaigns
and influencer partnerships,
along with a training program
for the new product launch.
We're in the final review stage
of the contracts.
Okay. Sounds good.
[giggles]
[♪ whimsical music plays]
Your Royal Highness.
The ceremonial robe has arrived
from the Royal Tailor Institution.
Are you that delighted?
No.
[clears throat]
-Where's Huiju?
-Ms. Seong is--
Your Royal Highness.
You must now observe
the proper forms of address.
[clears throat]
Where… is my wife?
What is she doing?
Your Ladyship!
STYLE
::cue()
[Hyejeong] Right.
Okay.
So once you put on
that crimson ceremonial robe…
-Crimson?
-Your eyeliner will smudge.
I finally get to wear red
and walk into the palace?
Here. The Ministry of Rites…
[Dayeong] Huiju!
My goodness.
Why are you here so early?
You and your assistant have little regard
for court or noble etiquette.
As a lady of a noble house,
I'll have to review everything myself.
[sighs]
Mmm… Not bad.
-Have her wedding shoes arrived?
-Yes, they have!
-My goodness!
-Oh, my!
[giggles] This is how
you protect your heels.
You'll be wearing them all day.
I see. That makes sense.
-[phone buzzes]
-Hmm?
Hey, Jeongwoo.
Are preparations going well?
You sure you don't want to call it off?
[scoffs]
-And if I say I do, would you help me?
-[chuckles]
Prime Minister Min.
I'll call you back.
Are you still not dressed?
Are you all right?
Why would I not be?
Then…
I shall wait.
Until the day you can
no longer restrain yourself.
Do we just wait here?
[♪ elegant music plays]
[gasps]
Huiju looks so pretty.
No, you're way prettier.
Congratulations on your nuptials.
-Congratulations.
[inhales sharply]
You're officially
the Grand Prince's wife. [giggles]
So? You like it?
[sighs]
STYLE
::cue()
[♪ traditional Korean music plays]
[officiant] All bow deeply!
All rise!
-[grunts]
-[gasps]
-You're okay.
-Your Ladyship.
Damn it…
[chuckles]
The bride and groom
shall exchange deep bows.
[♪ light orchestral music playing]
By sharing this wine,
you are now equals in status and soul.
I proclaim to Heaven and Earth
that you are joined as husband and wife.
[coughs]
Are you all right?
[strained] I'm fine.
[chuckles]
The father of the bride
shall now offer words of caution.
Show caution and reverence.
From early dawn until late at night,
let there be no deviation from command.
Yes.
I shall carry out your command faithfully.
Do not look down.
It makes you look weak.
-[cheering]
-[♪ marching music plays]
My goodness! Her Ladyship looks so…
No, I mean, Her Royal Highness. [giggles]
Her lips must be on the verge of spasming.
Just look at that perfect makeup.
Aren't you glad I used pink coral
instead of coral pink?
[Youngseon] Totally.
Just look at that massive crowd.
I don't think it was that big
for the Queen Mother.
Definitely not.
[coughs] Gosh. Why am I tearing up?
You look like your son's getting married.
Steward Kim, are you crying?
[inhales sharply]
[sighs]
Our Royal Highness is all grown up now.
-Hey, we crushed that.
-Gosh.
We crushed it!
Smile.
My jaw is about to snap
from all this smiling.
How do you do this for every single event?
Just hang in there.
STYLE
::cue()
We're almost there.
THE MARRIAGE PROCESSION OF
GRAND PRINCE I-AN
AND GRAND PRINCESS SEONG
[♪ melancholic music plays]
That is why I told you to veto it.
What is long suppressed
tends to erupt
in the most unexpected ways.
[camera shutters clicking]
-Congratulations.
The most sincere congratulations
to His Royal Highness
and Her Royal Highness.
Congratulations on achieving
nominal status.
[scoffs]
[♪ romantic music plays]
[Court Lady Choi] Your Majesty.
The Grand Prince
and his wife have arrived.
[Jeongwoo] Grand Prince I-AN.
On behalf of the people and the Cabinet,
I offer my most sincere congratulations
on your union.
-Congratulations.
Thank you, Prime Minister.
[sighs]
[Jeongwoo] Your Royal Highness.
On behalf of the people and the Cabinet,
I offer
my most sincere congratulations…
STYLE
::cue()
on your union.
-Congratulations.
Thank… [coughs]
[coughing]
Seong Huiju.
[♪ tense music plays]
-[exhales sharply]
-[clamoring]
Seong Huiju!
Huiju.
Huiju. Seong Huiju.
Seong Huiju!
PERFECT CROWN
[Huiju] Toxicity? Me?
[Jeongwoo] It looks deliberate.
I knew you would fail to protect her.
[Huiju] I made a mistake.
What are you doing? Calm down!
He's in danger right now!
[I-AN] Was I being too greedy again?
You're okay, right?
I thought you were dying.
I thought I lost you.
What are you doing?
The whole country saw me collapse live.
I can't be this pretty
when I'm discharged.
[I-AN] It's our first night
as a married couple.
Are you ready?
EPILOGUE
Don't make…
things difficult for Huiju.
What?
That's not
what she wants from you.
[sighs]
Then why wasn't it you?
What she aims to gain through marrying me.
You could provide the same.
Perhaps I have something
she wants
that you don't have?
Translated by Justin S. Kim
PERFECT CROWN